# LINDSAY STONER

Philadelphia, PA 19103

Email: lindsaybstoner@gmail.com | Phone: (914) 907-1699

Github Profile: lindsaybstoner | LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lindsay-stoner-9a85b212b

Portfolio: https://lindsaybstoner.github.io/Portfolio/

#### **SUMMARY**

Pursuing a Front End Web Developer position with full stack certification from the University of Pennsylvania (graduation end of July). Experiences as a lab manager and as a student in the bootcamp have enhanced my problem-solving, project management and analytical skills, as well as my attention to detail and ability to work either independently or in a group. I enjoy drawing upon my experience in technology, human behavior, research, and design to create a seamless and intuitive user interface.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, MySQL, Handlebars, HTML5, CSS, Flexbox, Bootstrap, R

Applications: Adobe Photoshop

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

University of Pennsylvania Social and Behavioral Science Initiative: Lab Coordinator August 2018 – Present

- Created infrastructure for new (\$750,000) research initiative including: researched and purchased new hardware/software; created SBSI website; developed protocol for grant and undergrad training applications; compiled and wrote the first annual report; advertised, vetted and triaged postdoctoral and lab coordinator applicants; created, advertised and presented research assistant training program
- Oversee and manage the laboratory's student research assistants, bi-monthly brown bag meetings, external speaker, yearly social event, website, participant pool, budget, subject payments, administration

#### Yale University Psychology Department: Research Assistant

June 2018 – August 2018

• Recruited children for developmental studies; conducted studies with children ages 3-7; recorded and analyzed data with R; designed stimuli and piloted personal research; presented weekly research updates to primary investigator, post-doctoral students, and RAs

#### Tufts University Psychology Department: Paid Research Assistant

May 2017 – August 2017

• Managed Comparative Cognition lab daily working with birds on visual/auditory cognition and perception; actively participated in weekly lab meeting with the post-doctoral students and primary investigator; learned basic coding; recorded data and then analyzed with postdoc

### Kenyon College Admissions: Senior Paid Fellow

August 2017 - May 2018

 Interviewed prospective students for admissions office of Kenyon College; wrote formal reviews of prospective students

# Kenyon College Psychology Department: Research Assistant

August 2017 – May 2018

• Managed Gaming and Mediated Experience (GAME) lab for professor, ran participants as an experimenter and as a confederate in research; participated in weekly lab meetings with RAs and primary investigator

### **EDUCATION**

# UPenn LPS Coding Bootcamp (Trilogy Educational Services) Full Stack Web Development

July 2019

• Currently enrolled in 24-week coding bootcamp

#### Kenyon College '18 (Psychology Major; Studio Art Minor) cum laude GPA 3.63

May 2018

• Dean's List, Comprehensive Examination/Psychology Major Senior Exercise: Distinction, Chapter of International Psi Chi Psychology Honors Society